<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Good Tech Wiki</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-0bec3d4d-37d8-46c9-b9ed-ed075f58bbcb/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-0bec3d4d-37d8-46c9-b9ed-ed075f58bbcb</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-0bec3d4d-37d8-46c9-b9ed-ed075f58bbcb/">&lt;p&gt;2INTRODUCTIONIn  order  to  facilitate  the  use  of  Binding  Corporate  Rules for  Controllers (BCR-C)  by  a corporate   group   or   a   group   of   enterprises   engaged   in   a   joint   economic   activity   for international  transfers  from  organisations  established  in  the  EU  to  organisations  within  the same  group  established  outside  the  EU,  the  Article 29  Working  Party  (WP29)  has  amended the Working Document 153 (which was adopted in 2008) setting up a table with the elements and  principles  to  be  found  in  Binding  Corporate  Rulesin  order  to  reflect  the  requirements referring  to  BCRsnow  expressly  set  outby  the Regulation  (EU)  2016/679  of  the  European Parliament  and  of  the  Council  of  27  April  2016  on  the  protection  of  natural  persons  with regard  to  the  processing  of  personal  data  and  on  the  free  movement  of  such  data,and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation / GDPR)1.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-1db962ea-53ce-4aab-87db-0e5e5c53d9f0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-1db962ea-53ce-4aab-87db-0e5e5c53d9f0</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-1db962ea-53ce-4aab-87db-0e5e5c53d9f0/">&lt;p&gt;Recommendation on the Standard Application form for Approval of Processor Binding Corporate Rules for the Transfer of Personal Data&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-22fd33c8-2960-4c2d-bd18-a2cff24cf21b/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-22fd33c8-2960-4c2d-bd18-a2cff24cf21b</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-22fd33c8-2960-4c2d-bd18-a2cff24cf21b/">&lt;p&gt;The International Working Group on Data Protection in Telecommunications (IWGDPT, a.k.a. “Berlin Group”) includes representatives from Data Protection Authorities and international organisations dealing with privacy matters from all over the world. It was founded in 1983 in the framework of the International Conference of Data Protection and Privacy Commissioners at the initiative of the Berlin Commissioner for Data Protection, who has since then been chairing the Group. The Group has since 1983 adopted numerous recommendations (“Common Positions” and “Working Papers”) aimed at improving the protection of privacy in telecommunications. Since the beginning of the 90s the Group has in particular focused on the protection of privacy on the Internet. More information about the Work of the Group and the documents adopted by the Group are available for download on the website of the Group at http://www.berlin-privacy-group.org&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-9c871b26-9cdc-43ce-bd2d-390c14dba4bd/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-9c871b26-9cdc-43ce-bd2d-390c14dba4bd</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-9c871b26-9cdc-43ce-bd2d-390c14dba4bd/">&lt;p&gt;This project gathers stories from across Latin America about the mass collection and processing of data that governments: businesses and we ourselves carry out to monitor our cities: homes: wallets and bodies.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-aa1f8f81-02c2-48b4-87af-2d38d63c2ca4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-aa1f8f81-02c2-48b4-87af-2d38d63c2ca4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-aa1f8f81-02c2-48b4-87af-2d38d63c2ca4/">&lt;p&gt;No body provided&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-f15b0cf8-94b4-442f-b1dd-23ffead0122d/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-f15b0cf8-94b4-442f-b1dd-23ffead0122d</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-f15b0cf8-94b4-442f-b1dd-23ffead0122d/">&lt;p&gt;The General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (‘GDPR’) allows personal data to be transferred outside the EEA only when the third country provides an “adequate level of protection” for the data (Art. 45) or when the controller adduces adequate safeguards with respect to the protection of privacy (Art. 46). Binding Corporate Rules (BCRs) are one of the ways in which such adequate safeguards (Art. 47) may be demonstrated by a group of undertakings, or group of enterprises engaged in a joint economic activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Article 64 GDPR, the use of BCRs as appropriate safeguards for international data transfers from the EEA requires the approval of the competent supervisory authority in accordance with the consistency mechanism set out in Article 63 without requiring any specific authorisation from a supervisory authority (Article 46.2.b GDPR). The following form is for use by companies seeking approval of BCRs. The form is based on papers previously issued by the Article 29 Working Party of European data protection authorities (the “Working Party”), and in particular WP133, and it is intended to help applicants demonstrate how to meet the requirements set out in Article 47 GDPR and WP 256.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html"></title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-fae97a14-42ab-442b-be3c-6b71a3ec7db4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="" /><published>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T06:56:12+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-fae97a14-42ab-442b-be3c-6b71a3ec7db4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020-02-13-fae97a14-42ab-442b-be3c-6b71a3ec7db4/">&lt;p&gt;In  order  to  facilitate  the  use  of  Binding  Corporate  Rules  for  Processors  (BCR-P)  by  a  corporate   group   or   a   group   of   enterprises   engaged   in   a   joint   economic   activity   for   international  transfers  from  organisations  established  in  the  EU  to  organisations  within  the  same  group  established  outside  the  EU,  the  Article  29  Working  Party  (WP29)  has  amended  the Working Document 195 (which was adopted in 2012) setting up a table with the elements and  principles  to  be  found  in  Binding  Corporate  Rules  in  order  to  reflect  the  requirements referring  to  BCRs  now  expressly  set  out  in Regulation  (EU)  2016/679  of  the  European  Parliament  and  of  the  Council  of  27  April  2016  on  the  protection  of  natural  persons  with  regard  to  the  processing  of  personal  data  and  on  the  free  movement  of  such  data,and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation / GDPR).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Algorithmic Justice League</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/000a0b66-9df0-4f0e-8112-58c6e7a2ba6c/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Algorithmic Justice League" /><published>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/000a0b66-9df0-4f0e-8112-58c6e7a2ba6c</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/000a0b66-9df0-4f0e-8112-58c6e7a2ba6c/">&lt;p&gt;FIGHT ALGORITHMIC DISCRIMINATION&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">FIGHT ALGORITHMIC DISCRIMINATION</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Good ID</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/001a22fc-0144-4cc5-b3f3-4d14b19591c3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Good ID" /><published>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/001a22fc-0144-4cc5-b3f3-4d14b19591c3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/001a22fc-0144-4cc5-b3f3-4d14b19591c3/">&lt;p&gt;Through conversation and collaborative initiatives: the #GoodID movement will explore the different interests of people: governments: and businesses: learn from implementation: and build better systems that work for governments: business and individuals.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Through conversation and collaborative initiatives: the #GoodID movement will explore the different interests of people: governments: and businesses: learn from implementation: and build better systems that work for governments: business and individuals.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TRUSTe EU-US Privacy Shield Solutions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/001dd446-3df0-42ad-9df0-48dd80a2998d/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TRUSTe EU-US Privacy Shield Solutions" /><published>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</published><updated>2020-02-13T00:00:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/001dd446-3df0-42ad-9df0-48dd80a2998d</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/001dd446-3df0-42ad-9df0-48dd80a2998d/">&lt;p&gt;Demonstrate EU-US Privacy Shield compliance for customer and employee data transfers with an independent third party review and verification.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Demonstrate EU-US Privacy Shield compliance for customer and employee data transfers with an independent third party review and verification.</summary></entry></feed>